

THOMAS CONNOLE

Omaha, NE 68124 402-596-5295 th.connole@gmail.com

Dedicated, hardworking, and motivated Information Technology Professional with experience in contributing to an IT project for a Fortune 500 company and Software Development for a global aerospace and defense technology company. I have just started my journey in my career path, but my knowledge and education in the field has quickly grown. I look forward to my ever-growing knowledge base and increasing my experience in the IT field, with a focus on Computer Science and Software Development.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer

10/2020 to Present

Northrop Grumman

Bellevue, NE

- Full-stack develop RECAP project
- Programming Languages: Java, Python, Javascript, Typescript, & bash
- Tools: GIT, bitbucket, Atlassian tool, Fortify, VScode, jenkins, gradle, docker, Oracle DB, Cypress, Jasmine, etc...
- Linux

Software Engineer

07/2019 to 10/2020

Teksystems

Bellevue, NE

- · Contractor for Northrop Grumman SEMS III contract
- Agile and Kanban Development and application sustainment
- Knowledge of development tools: GIT, atlassian Tools (jira, confluence), Fortify, Sonar, jenkins, Ansible,
 VisualWeather, DI2E, Bitbucket, Mercurial, Intellij, and PostgresSQL
- Knowledge of programming languages: Python, Java, Javascript, HTML, CSS, XML, JSON, ActionScript, SQL, bash, php

Manager: Crystal Larson | SEMS III AFW-WEBS Software Lead crystal.larson@ngc.com

Systems Engineer Intern

09/2017 to 07/2019

Union Pacific

Omaha, NE

Worked at the computer build center focusing on the Windows 10 upgrade project.

- · Providing general support of internal customer client computing devices, software and peripherals
- · Windows administration
- Software/hardware installation
- Internal Software development
- · Professional communication with internal customers and project planning

Manager: Lonnie Westerman Irwester@up.com

SKILLS

Development tools: Atlassian Tools, DI2E DevTool, GIT, IntelliJ, VScode, tmux, ssh, Microsoft Suite

Windows / Linux Administration

Software / Hardware Installation

Languages: Python , Java, JavaScript, TypeScript, C, bash, SQL, JSON

Front end development: HTML / CSS, Angular, material, NGRX

Information Security: Policy, Forensic Toolkit, Wireshark

Testing: Regression, unit (junit, jasmine, unittest), Front-end (Selenium, Cypress)

EDUCATION

University of Nebraska at Omaha

Bachelor's Computer Science (minor Information Assurance) Omaha, NE 08/2015 to 05/2019

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Hobbies

- Software Development
- Computer Hardware
- 3D printing
- Rock Climbing
- Tabletop gaming

Links:

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/thomas-connole-baa593161

Capstone project: https://jeroo.org/